{
    "subject": "resource/Clark_Haggans",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1977-01-10",
    "human_readable": "Clark Haggans was born on January 10, 1977.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8780364990234375,
            "question": "When was Clark Haggans born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8261047601699829,
            "question": "Which century was Clark Haggans born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7725631594657898,
            "question": "How old was Clark Haggans on January 10th, 2023?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714164853096008,
            "question": "What month was Clark Haggans born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7591297030448914,
            "question": "What is Clark Haggans' birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7500045895576477,
            "question": "Is Clark Haggans a January baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7455142140388489,
            "question": "What is Clark Haggans' birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7275947332382202,
            "question": "On what day of the month was Clark Haggans born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44724926352500916,
            "question": "In what year did Clark Haggans come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3838427662849426,
            "question": "Is Clark Haggans' birthday in December?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clark Haggans was born on January 10, 1977.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1499_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Clark Haggans come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1499_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what day of the month was Clark Haggans born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1499_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Clark Haggans' birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1499_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1499_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Clark Haggans was born on January 10, 1977. This information is supported by multiple files, including `8.txt`, `28.txt`, and `4.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}